https://insideracing.com.ph/privacy-policy/

INSIDERACING NATION Privacy Statement
What’s New in the Updated Privacy Statement? We have updated the privacy statement applicable to our online and mobile websites, digital services, and applications and clarified data collection, usage and sharing practices among INSIDERACING and its marketing partners. Please take the time to read the full privacy statement. You consent to the data collection, use, disclosure and storage practices described in this privacy statement when you use
INSIDERACING NATION (as described below), including when you access any content or videos.
Thank you for visiting INSIDERACING NATION,
CAMBA Motohaus Inc. (“CMI”, “we”, “us” or “our”) operates INSIDERACING.COM.PH is a general audience site and includes this website (including its subdomains) and associated applications and digital services (such as mobile and other device applications), and other associated offerings that are owned, offered or operated by or on behalf of CMI. Your privacy is important to us. As such, we provide this privacy statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at INSIDERACING NATION (IR NATION) App. Please be advised that the practices described in this privacy policy apply only to information gathered through and in connection with INSIDERACING NATION.
The Information We Collect
We receive both information that is directly provided to us, such as personal information you provide when you visit IR NATION, and information that is passively or automatically collected from you, such as anonymous information collected from your device. In this privacy statement, we refer to all of this as the “Information.”
Information You Provide to Us. At IR NATIOM, you can register, enter contests, express an opinion, or participate in one of our “ NATION” communities. In the course of these various offerings, we often seek to collect from you various forms of Information, such as: name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number. In addition, we may have access to information that identifies your mobile device and telecommunications carrier.
Information That is Passively or Automatically Collected. We, and our “Partners” who include our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and distribution or other partners may use automated means to collect various types of Information about you, your computer or other device used to access IR NATION. A representative, non-exhaustive list of the types of automatically collected Information may include the name of your Internet service provider and domains used by such providers, mobile network, device identifiers (such as Apple IDFA or an Android Advertising ID), device settings, browser settings, the pages of IR NATION you have visited, the type of handheld or mobile device used to view IR NATION
(e.g., iOS, Android), location information, and the content and advertisements you have accessed, seen, forwarded and/or clicked on. Please see the Section titled Cookies, and Other User and Ad-Targeting Technologies for more information about how the foregoing Information may be collected and used.
Geo-location Information. If you are accessing IR NATION from a mobile device you may be asked to share your precise (GPS level) geo-location information with us so we can customize your experience on IR NATION or on other services, when we work with a Partner such as a third party mobile ad platform. If you agree to such collection, in most cases, you will be able to turn off such data collection at any time by accessing the privacy settings of your mobile device and/or through the settings in the applicable mobile application.
Information Collected By and From Social Media Services and Other Third Party Platforms. You also can engage with our content, such as video and other offerings, on or through social media services or other third-party platforms and social networking sites, such as Facebook, or other third-party social media plug-ins, integrations and applications. When you engage with our content on or through social media services or other third party platforms, plug-ins, integrations or applications, you may allow us to have access to certain Information in your profile. This may include your name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, an ID associated with the applicable third party platform or social media account user files, like photos and videos, your list of friends or connections, people you follow and/or who follow you, or your posts or the ‘likes’. For a description of how social media services and other third party platforms, plug-ins, integrations or applications handle your information, please refer to their respective privacy policies and terms of use, which may permit you to modify your privacy settings.
When we interact with you through our content on third party websites, applications, integrations or platforms, we may obtain any information regarding your interaction with that content, such as content you have viewed, your game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on.
How We Use the Information
We, along with our Partners, may use the Information to:
provide and communicate with you about IR NATION, to contact you about your account with us,
fulfill your requests for our services, including without limitation requests for notifications,
respond to your inquiries, and notify you if you have won one of our contests,
communicate with you about other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you,
enforce the legal terms (including without limitation this privacy statement and our terms of use) that govern your use of IR NATION, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the information.
provide technical support for IR NATION
prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities (including, without limitation, copyright infringement) on or through IR NATION,
protect the safety of our users,
customize or personalize ads, offers and content made available to you based on your visits to and/or usage of IR NATION or other online or mobile websites, applications, platforms or services, and analyze the performance of those ads, offers and content, as well as your interaction with them,
perform analysis regarding how you use IR NATION or any part thereof,
send Invitations or emails if you use these services, to your designated recipients.
When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our applications or websites, (3) contact you through the social media service or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards, and (4) enable you to share your experience and content via social media services. When you provide information about yourself to us through an application, on our sites, or on social media services or other third party platforms, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we
cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.
We or a Partner may use “cookies” or similar technologies to associate certain of the Information with a unique identifier that then associates the Information with your device or browser. For information about how these technologies work and how we may use them, please go to the Section titled Cookies, And Other Users and Ad-Targeting Technologies.
Sometimes, we may associate cookies with the Information, including de-identified, “hashed,” or anonymous versions of Information you have provided (such as during registration), in order to send or help our Partners send ads and offers based on your presumed interests or demographic information.
We may combine any of the Information we collect, for any of the above purposes, and may sometimes enhance the Information with other information that we obtain from third party sources. Please also be aware that if you choose to submit Information or content for publication (e.g., a letter to our editors, comments sent to our writers and/or personalities, a posting to a blog or a discussion board, or a video), we may publish that Information and content, along with other Information about you (such as your name, screen name or location). Likewise, if you register and create a profile with IR NATION, the screen name you select as well as other content you submit to your profile (e.g., photos, comments, video, reviews) will be displayed publicly on IR NATION, is searchable, can be found by third parties and may be reused and redistributed by us in our sole discretion.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
We may disclose the Information as follows:
To service providers or Partners that we have engaged to perform business-related functions on our behalf. This may include service providers that: (a) conduct research and analytics; (b) create content; (c) provide customer, technical or operational support; (d) conduct or support marketing (such as email or advertising platforms); (e) fulfill orders and user requests; (f) handle payments; (g) host IR NATION, forums and online communities; (h) administer contests; (i) maintain databases; (j) send or support online or mobile advertising; and (k) otherwise support IR NATION.
In response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena, a law enforcement or government agency’s request or similar request, or where we believe in our sole discretion it is necessary
With third parties in order to investigate, prevent, or take action ( in our sole discretion) regarding potentially illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to any person, us, or IR NATION, or violations of our policies, the law or our Terms of Use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing IR NATION and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements.
We may transfer some or all of your Information if we, or one of our business units, undergoes a business transition, like a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or part of our assets, or if a substantial portion of our or of a business unit’s assets is sold or merged in this way.
We may share the Information with affiliates, so they can provide, improve and communicate with you about their own, or their marketing partners’ products and services.
We may share the Information with unaffiliated Partners and third parties (e.g., our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that wish to market products or services to you. In addition, we may disclose Information that identifies your mobile device, telecommunications carrier and information regarding your access/use of IR NATION mobile applications to CMI’s wireless communications partner.
If you wish to opt out from such sharing please visit the How to Contact Us/Opting Out of Marketing Communications section below for further instructions.
Please note that IR NATION may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, promotions, games, applications, or social network integrations) that is sponsored or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain information from their visitors. We have no control over these third parties’ use of this information, which is subject to their own privacy policies.
Cookies and Other User and Ad-Targeting Technologies
We may use cookies and other technologies both to provide our services to you and to advertise to you. We may also work with Partners to help them advertise to you when you visit other websites or mobile applications, and to help them perform user analytics. These technologies may also be used to analyze how our users interact with advertising on IR NATION and elsewhere, and more generally, to learn more about our users and what services or offers you might prefer to receive. We describe some of these technologies below.
Cookies. To enhance your online experience, we may use “cookies”, “web beacons” or other tracking technologies. Cookies are text files placed in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. We use cookies or other tracking technologies to understand site and Internet usage and to improve or customize the products, content, offerings, services or advertisements on IR NATION. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on IR NATION (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to IR NATION), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on IR NATION. We also may use cookies or other tracking technologies to help us offer you products, content, offering s, or services that may be of interest to you and to deliver relevant advertising when you visit IR NATION, an affiliate’s website, or when you visit other websites or applications. We or a third party platform with whom we work may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized content, offers, services or advertisements on IR NATIOM or other sites. These cookies contain no information intended to identify you personally. The cookies may be associated with de-identified demographic or other data linked to or derived from data you voluntarily have submitted to us (e.g., your email address) that we may share with a service provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form.
We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our Partners also may use cookies or other tracking technologies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through IR NATION. This also helps us, our service providers and Partners provide more relevant advertising. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy statement.
Synching Cookies and Identifiers. We may work with our Partners (for instance, third party ad platforms) to synchronize unique, anonymous identifiers (such as those associated with cookies) in order to match our Partner’s uniquely coded user identifiers to our own. We may do this, for instance, to enhance data points about a particular unique browser or device, and thus enable us or others to send ads that are more relevant, match users to their likely product interests, or better synchronize, cap, or optimize advertising.
Locally Stored Objects. IR NATION may employ locally stored objects (“LSOs”) and other client side storage tracking technologies in certain situations where they help to provide a better user experience, such as to remember settings, preferences and usage similar to browser cookies, or in order to target or help our Partners target ads, analyze ads performance, or perform user, website or market analytics. For LSOs utilized by Adobe Flash you can access your Flash management tools from Adobe’s website. In addition, some, but not all browsers, provide the ability to remove LSOs, sometimes within cookie and privacy settings.
Disabling Cookies. Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies. You may be able to set your browser to warn you before accepting certain cookies or to refuse certain cookies. However, if you disable the use of cookies in your web browser, some features of IR NATION may be difficult to use or inoperable.
We may work with certain third-party companies that use techniques other than HTTP cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity, including those integrated with IR NATION. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these techniques, and those browser settings that block conventional cookies may have no effect on such techniques. To learn more about Interest-Based Advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising by those third parties that are members of DAA’s opt-out program, please go to http://www.aboutads.info.
Web Beacons. We and our Partners may also use “web beacons” or clear GIFs, or similar technologies, which are small pieces of code placed on a web page or in an email, to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page or email. For example, web beacons may be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. Web beacons may also be used to provide information on the effectiveness of our email campaigns (e.g., open rates, clicks, forwards, etc.).
Mobile Device Identifiers and SDKs. We also sometimes use, or partner with publishers, publisher-facing, or app developer platforms that use mobile Software Development Kits (“SDKs”), or use an SDK with a mobile app that we offer, to collect Information, such as mobile identifiers (e.g., IDFAs and Android Advertising IDs), and Information connected to how mobile devices interact with IR NATION products and services and those using IR NATION. A mobile SDK is the mobile app version of a web beacon (see “Web Beacons” above). The SDK is a bit of computer code that app developers can include in their apps to enable ads to be shown, data to be collected, and related services or analytics to be performed. We may use this technology to deliver or help our Partners deliver certain advertising through mobile applications and browsers based on information associated with your mobile device. If you’d like to opt-out from having ads tailored to you in this way on your mobile device, please follow the instructions in the “Your Ad Choices” section below.
By visiting IR NATION, whether as a registered user or otherwise, you acknowledge, and agree that you are giving us your consent to track your activities and your use of IR NATION through the technologies described above, as well as similar technologies developed in the future, and that we may use such tracking technologies in the emails we send to you.
Our unaffiliated Partners and third parties may themselves set and access their own tracking technologies when you visit IR NATION and they may have access to information about you and your online activities over time and across different websites or applications when you use IR NATION. Their use of such tracking technologies is not in our control and is subject to their own privacy policies.
Linked Services
IR NATION may contain links to or integrations with other sites such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and other media services and platforms, whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
Data Security
We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures designed to help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the Information we collect online. These safeguards vary based on the sensitivity of the information that we collect and store.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of Information, we cannot assure you that Information that will never be disclosed, altered or destroyed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy statement.
How You Can Access or Correct Information
Access to certain personal Information that is collected from IR NATION and that we maintain may be available to you. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our site, you can access that account to review the information you provided.
You may also send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting access to or correction of your personal Information. Please include your registration information for IR NATION, such as first name, last name, e-mail address in the request. We may ask you to provide additional information for identity verification purposes, or to verify that you are in possession of an applicable email account.
Updates & Effective Date
From time to time, we may update this privacy statement. We will notify you about material changes by either sending an email message to the email address you most recently provided to us or by prominently posting a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this statement so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it.
The Privacy Statement posted on this site was updated March 23, 2018.
© 2018 Camba Motohaus Inc.
Download fromApple App Store
Download fromGoogle Play
Featured Stories
Walter’s Solo Ride
Donald Duck- Themed Honda Wave from Cebu City
Momentous Victory for
Gab Valenciano and Suzuki-Wheeltek
Pirelli Cup Wraps Up another Good Season
Batmobile-inspired Super Show Scoot from Tiaong, Quezon
Alex Marquez Talks about His and Marc’s Riding Style
CST Caps Off 2020 with a new Highway-terrain
Moto Street Tire
Pertua Introduces New Powertec Matic and Sponsors Scooter Class of MotoIR Practice Day
Lucas Oil is looking forward to race in 2021
PCX Cebu Xclusive
Skip to toolbar
About WordPressWordPress.orgDocumentationSupportFeedbackLog InRegisterWhat The Filepage.phpTemplate Partspartial/billboard-ads.phpPowered by Never5page.php
